question_data = [
    {"category": "Science & Nature", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "The Neanderthals were a direct ancestor of modern humans.", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Film", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                                      "question": "Han Solo&#039;s co-pilot and best friend, &quot;Chewbacca&quot;, is an Ewok.",
                                      "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "History", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard",
     "question": "Japan was part of the Allied Powers during World War I.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Music", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
                                       "question": "Arcade Fire&#039;s &#039;The Suburbs&#039; won the Album of the Year award in the 2011 Grammys.",
                                       "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "History", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard",
     "question": "The Kingdom of Prussia briefly held land in Estonia.", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                                      "question": "In &quot;Super Mario 64&quot;, collecting 100 coins on a level will give you a 1-UP.",
                                      "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Politics", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "The S in Harry S. Truman stands for &quot;Samuel&quot;.", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
                                      "question": "The vapor produced by e-cigarettes is actually water.",
                                      "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Music", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "American rapper Dr. Dre actually has a Ph.D. doctorate.", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "Geography", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
                                      "question": "The longest place named in the United States is Lake Chargoggagoggmanchauggagoggchaubunagungamaugg, located near Webster, MA.",
                                      "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Studio Ghibli is a Japanese animation studio responsible for the films &quot;Wolf Children&quot; and &quot;The Boy and the Beast&quot;.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Luigi is taller than Mario?", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Music", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "Ashley Frangipane performs under the stage name Halsey.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Art", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
                                       "question": "Pablo Picasso is one of the founding fathers of &quot;Cubism.&quot;",
                                       "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard",
     "question": "In &quot;Portal 2&quot;, Cave Johnson started out Aperture Science as a shower curtain company.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "In &quot;Super Mario 3D World&quot;, the Double Cherry power-up originated from a developer accidentally making two characters controllable.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "History", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "United States President John F. Kennedy was assassinated during his presidential motorcade in Atlanta, Georgia on November 22nd, 1963.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "Kissing someone for one minute burns about 2 calories.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Geography", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
                                       "question": "There exists an island named &quot;Java&quot;.",
                                       "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "The French word to travel is &quot;Travail&quot;", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "Geography", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                                      "question": "Toronto is the capital city of the North American country of Canada.",
                                      "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Comics", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "In the webcomic Homestuck, the first character introduced is Dave Strider.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Board Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "There is a Donald Trump Board Game, which was made in 1989.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Film", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                                       "question": "In the original Star Wars trilogy, Alec Guinness provided the voice for Darth Vader.",
                                       "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Science: Gadgets", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Microphones can be used not only to pick up sound, but also to project sound similar to a speaker.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Mythology", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "In Greek mythology, Hera is the goddess of harvest.", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                                      "question": "In Pok&eacute;mon Sun and Moon, a male Salandit can evolve to a Salazzle.",
                                      "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Politics", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "George W. Bush lost the popular vote in the 2004 United States presidential election.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Geography", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "Liechtenstein does not have an airport.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Science & Nature", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "An Astronomical Unit is the distance between Earth and the Moon.", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Music", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                                      "question": "Stevie Wonder&#039;s real name is Stevland Hardaway Morris.",
                                      "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Celebrities", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Marilyn Monroe was born on July 1, 1926.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "In Pok&eacute;mon, Arbok evolves into Seviper.", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Television", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard",
                                      "question": "The Klingon home planet is Qo&#039;noS.", "correct_answer": "True",
                                      "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Sports", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "Wilt Chamberlain scored his infamous 100-point-game against the New York Knicks in 1962.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "The ADAM collecters in the Bioshock series are known as Little Sisters.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
                                       "question": "&quot;Santa Claus&quot; is a variety of melon.",
                                       "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Celebrities", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Tupac Shakur died due to complications from being stabbed in 1996.", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                                      "question": "&quot;27 Club&quot; is a term used to refer to a list of famous actors, musicians, and artists who died at the age of 27.",
                                      "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Geography", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Nova Scotia is on the east coast of Canada.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
                                       "question": "The pickled gherkin was first added to hamburgers because a US health law required all fast-food to include a source of Vitamin C.",
                                       "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Vietnam&#039;s national flag is a red star in front of a yellow background.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Vehicles", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard",
     "question": "The term &quot;GTO&quot; was originated by Ferrari?", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
                                       "question": "&quot;Buffalo buffalo Buffalo buffalo buffalo buffalo Buffalo buffalo.&quot; is a grammatically correct sentence.",
                                       "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Television", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "&quot;The Simpsons&quot; family is named after creator Matt Groening&#039;s real family.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "In the game &quot;Until Dawn&quot; Emily is the only playable character who can be killed by another playable character directly.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Music", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "&quot;Neutral Milk Hotel&quot; is a real band.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
                                       "question": "Instant mashed potatoes were invented by Canadian Edward Asselbergs in 1962.",
                                       "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "History", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "Franz Joseph I was the last emperor of Austria.", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Music", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
                                      "question": "Green Day&#039;s album &#039;American Idiot&#039; is considered a &quot;punk rock opera.&quot;",
                                      "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}
]
